Yes, go ahead.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Yes, yes. Arm stretch.
Yeah. - Okay.
Oh, thank you, that's cute.
Here you go.
Yeah, fingers and feet, a little bit.
Okay.
Uh, quickly, arm stretching.
Yeah, it's so good.
Try lifting your legs up.
Oh, wait a minute.
Okay.
Still, good work.
Welcome.
What's this? What is it?
Julie, what is this?
What's this pose?
Congratulations.
I don't want to change for a second.
Thank you for all your hard work.
I've never had a proper part-time job.
I've always wanted to do something like this.
I'm so glad I got to wear it today.
I'll definitely go again with the members next time.
I'm sure I'll be able to see that you're the same shade as me at that time.
I'm looking forward to it.
You can also make beauty products for the body?
Yes, I do.
I make a cheeseburger called the Cheeseburger.
It's a cheese hamburger.
I love hamburgers.
They were very particular about the design.
Please come hungry.
Please, please, please.
Please come and make me say thank you, please, thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
I've done my homework, checked the websites of the other collaborators.
I thought it was soft.
I've never worked with rice before, and I was going to work at the recital, but it said I had to be a university student, so I couldn't do it.
That's great.
What else? Welcome.
Nice.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
How was it?
It's my first time in uniform.
I've always wanted to wear this hat.
I'm really looking forward to it.
The café
I wanted to do a collaboration café.
I've even named the menu, but I'm really excited about it, and I've always wanted to do a collaboration café.
I've even given them the name of the menu
We put a lot of energy into it and had a family meeting.
We made up a lot of really weird names, so I don't know what will happen with three of them.
I don't know how it will turn out with three menu names.
I'm looking forward to seeing which one it turns out to be.
Thank you very much.
Please come and visit us.
It's so cute.
Very nice.
Thank you.
Last one.
Look at me.
Swing this way.
Thank you.
That's one of them.
Cute.
Both.
Nakai-san's pose...
Now there's two of them.
Thank you for your hard work.
How was it?
There are so many poses.
Poses like, "Come this way, please".
You did a lot of poses.
I felt like I was working part-time.
How do you like it? Try it on like that.
I really feel like I could be working right now.
I'm glad I've never had a part-time job before.
What is your collaboration menu like?
My collaboration menu is sweets? My collaboration menu is a pastry brûlée.
I love it, so I hope a lot of people will enjoy it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes, please enjoy it. Thank you very much. Thank you for your hard work.
I've got this apron.
It reminds me of when I was working part-time.
I'm feeling nostalgic.
I wanted to work there once.
When I was in high school.
At a supermarket?
Yes, I really wanted to.
I was even thinking about going for an interview.
I'm glad I got to wear this.
I'm also really happy to be able to give my own lectures on the menu.
I'm really happy that you're offering it.
I'm just waiting to see the excitement in everyone's eyes.
Thank you very much.
Last player's expression.
The expression on Rast's face.
Nice! That expression is perfect.
The expression on the last player's face
The expression on the last player's face.
Nice! Tight last batch.
The expression on the last player's face
Expression of the last player
Facial expressions of the last players.
On the left.
Suddenly he said...
He's strong.
They're watching us.
Thank you very much.
How was it?
It was a lot of fun.
I've had a lot of advice from you before I went into the camp.
I've never worn such a pretty thing before, so I'm glad it's clean!
For the collaboration menu, I suggested miso ramen, which I love.
I thought it would be limited to sweets.
It's a big ramen!
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes, thank you very much.
Yes, of course.
Thank you very much. Oh! Aah!
That's good!
Thank you.
Onion.
Onions.
Good!
Yes, yes.
Is this it? This? That's nice and pretty.
This one.
That's it.
It's so cute.
It's a part-time job.
Cute.
Looks good.
Can I get a part-time job?
I can.
Good work!
What? You're wearing an apron like this.
I've never dressed like this before.
It was my first time and I was a bit nervous.
But it was fun, a lot of fun.
I'm a little embarrassed when I think that this will be used as Swipara's merchandise
I'm a little embarrassed.
I'm so happy!
I'm glad that my collaboration menu
It's like a melon soda with a bear in it.
So this is my hair with the bear in mind.
I came up with an amazing menu name.
Mr. Blue's melon soda, Chef Kumatan's best drink.
Chef Kumatan's best drink...
It's got a big, big, big smile on the side.
Like this.
Yes, sir!
The name of the menu is genius.
I think.
Well, I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you very much.
I think this is Kambachi.
Yes, Kambachi.
Kambachi.
It will be Kambachi.
Kambachi, I think.
I will be kanbachis. I will be the children. You, you, you. I will be the children.
Children, lots of children.
Me, children.
You, you, you.
You, you.
Hey, hey.
Thank you very much. Thank you, thank you, thank you.
I was really happy when I first heard about you.
I had originally been going to eat at Sweets Paradise with my family.
I also went to Sweets Paradise for dinner with the members for the first time after I became a member of Niajun.
That was the first time I learned that Micchan could eat so much food.
It was also at Sweets Paradise that we had our first dinner together and talked about all sorts of things.
We are really happy to be collaborating with Sweets Paradise.
Each member had their own menu for the collaboration, and I really liked the drinks.
I hope everyone can enjoy the drinks.
It's the Apple guy.
That's so cute! - I did that.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
Good work, sir.
Thank you very much.
How was the filming?
It was good.
This hat says "Sweets Paradise" on it.
It's a bit like working part-time.
I was so excited.
Everyone got the shirt pattern wrong, or the hat pattern wrong, etc. I'm really looking forward to the finished product. I'm really looking forward to it.
Colorfully conceived.
Yes, I did. I made a juice with colourful jellies in it.
I usually eat colourful things, so I can have it for the members and so on.
No, Mai told me that colourful food is better for Mai.
I thought that was true too, so I invented it.
What do you usually eat that's colourful?
What? Sweets from overseas.
And colourful drinks.
I like colourful and exciting food.
I look forward to it when I see it on the menu.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Thank you very much.
Nice.
I can touch the machine.
Very nice. Nice! And touching the mouse.
Very nice.
Welcome, welcome.
Welcome, just like that.
Welcome.
Yes, please come in.
Yes, come in.
Oh, shit, oh, shit, yes, come in, come in, come in, come in, come in, come in, come in, come in, come in, come in, come in, come in. Are you filming?
Laughs.
Yeah, that's what I'm doing, too.
It's perfect.
Did you get it?
How was the filming?
Well, you know...
I had a lot of fun filming with a lot of people talking to me.
I had a lot of fun filming.
But when I put on a proper outfit like this
I feel a different kind of tension.
It's fun, but
I have to do my best to deliver the products properly
I have to do my best to deliver the product properly.
I came up with the idea of Thai milk tea myself.
I like Thailand, don't I?
That's why I want to make Thai food.
I told you that I wanted to make Thai food.
It has tapioca in it.
Thai traditional milk tea with tapioca in it.
I'll produce it for you.
Please have a cup.
It's lovely.
Very nice.
Cute Nice cute Yes, very nice.
Cute nice cute
Nice cute
Cute
Oh, yes, thank you
Yes, sir.
Last one.
Se-no.
Nice and cute.
Nice curtains, nice curtains.
Good.
How was the shoot?
The costumes were very colourful and the shirts were different colours for the different members, which was cute.
I was very happy that we were able to shoot in a very fun atmosphere.
It was the first time we created a new word with 'nice kawaii'.
What was the collaboration menu like?
I love matcha very, very much, so we collaborated on that and matcha,
I'm going to shoot Yuka's Matcha Latte at the collaboration café, and Yuka's Matcha Latte at the club café.
I'm sure you'll all have a great reaction to it, so please drink it!
Thank you very much.
Bye bye!
Thank you very much. Bye bye.
See you in the next video.
Nice wave.
Yeah. - Yeah.
There you go.
Oh, good.
Go get the battery.
Oh, my goodness.
It's so good.
Oh, my God.
Here it comes, it's so cute.
I can't wait to see it.
Thank you very much.
How was it?
The uniforms, the hats, the logo...
The hat and the logo are really cute,
I've actually had a part-time job before, so the uniform really brings back memories.
I didn't work at Suipura, but I worked in a restaurant,
I remember how I used to do things like this, and it made me feel really nostalgic.
I'm looking forward to seeing the finished collaborative products.
I'm looking forward to seeing the finished product.
I'm really looking forward to seeing what it will look like when it's made into merchandise.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Thank you very much.
And the heart pose...
He gave it to me.
Thank you.
Thank you, come here for a second, and they gave me the heart pose, too.
Turn around a little bit.
That looks good.
Let's do the front.
Nice.
Two hands, boss.
Yes, ma'am.
Relax, yes. Welcome.
Yes, that's all then. Thank you very much.
What do you think of your outfit?
Well, it was my first time to wear an apron like this, and I was happy to wear it for the first time, although I feel like I've already had a part-time job.
Of course, you've never had a part-time job before, have you?
No, it was my first time, and it was also the first time I posed as if to say 'Welcome'.
It was something new and fresh.
There are also costumes and uniforms to wear in the shop, aren't there?
Yes, it seems so.
They're cute, these checks.
They're all different colours.
I had the red check.
- Thank you very much.